Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/zin-nguyen-02336a140 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Website Building
WordPress
Mobile Application Design

Zin Nguyen

Senior UI/UX Designer

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Hello, I'm Zin - a freelance designer. Currently, i am working for a Japanese company.

I have more than 12 years experience in the digital world. I work will well-established companies but I also work major brands and start-ups. Well, everybody is welcome!

I have been a professional UI/UX, Web and Graphic designer for the past years, working on projects for agencies and various organisations (MTV, GAMELOFT Vietnam, STANLEY, DeWALT, JX Prints Singapore, DT ASIA Singapore, LOTTE Vietnam, Pizza 4P's, Hoang Phuc International...).

Experience

freec.asia - The Leading Recruitment Al Platform Senior UI/UX Designer July 2021 - Present (3 years 9 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

ZinArt
UI/UX Designer
January 2010 - Present (15 years 3 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Alive Vietnam
Senior UI/UX Designer
June 2017 - April 2021 (3 years 11 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- TIO CITI WILLIT CITY, VIETLIAITI
- Web/App design (UI/UX Design)
- Graphic design

DT Asia Pte Ltd Creative Designer

- Meet with clients and brainstorm ideas for wireframes, mockups

January 2015 - December 2019 (5 years)

Singapore, Singapore

- Web design (UI Design)
- Graphic design

JX Prints Pte Ltd

Graphic Designer

March 2014 - December 2019 (5 years 10 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Hoang Phuc International

Digital Technical Officer

March 2011 - March 2014 (3 years 1 month)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Manage the entire website system (brand, e-commerce website)
- Web design (UI Design)
- Graphic design

Education

Ton Duc Thang University

Information Technology · (2006 - 2010)

Raffles Academy

Web Designer · (2009 - 2010)

Nhat Nghe Academy

Website Developer · (2009 - 2009)

VNUHCM - University of Science

Graphic Designer · (2007 - 2009)